driver-soft.com 2019-07-31

# Driver Genius - Privacy Statement

Collection and use of information

In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information: 

Use of cookies: 

When you visit Driver-Soft.com, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user account details, preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, Driver-Soft.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

Log information: 

When you use Driver-Soft.com, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

Driver-Soft.com processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We only process personal information to provide our own services. 

Choices for personal information: 

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

Information security: 

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to Driver-Soft.com. employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

Data integrity: 

Driver-Soft.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

How We Use Your Information: 

We use your personally identifiable information to fulfill purchases that you make through our Sites or Services, for marketing purposes, to provide service and support, and to improve the quality and type of applications we make available via our products. We share the information with affiliates and other reputable organizations for service, support and marketing purposes.

If you provide us with your postal or e-mail address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information about products, services and upcoming events. We may share your information with select business partners so that they may offer products and services that we believe will be attractive to our customers and to those who have subscribed to our mailing list.

In addition, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties in order to: (i) respond to the requests of police and governmental authorities, (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order, (iii) help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect our rights or (iv) protect the personal safety of our employees and third parties. We may also share your information with or transfer it to third parties for business reasons, such as in the context of the sale or merger of our company or business.

Aggregate, anonymous data collected is statistical in nature, and does not include personally identifiable information. This data may be used to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our Services.. 

Changes to this policy: 

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
